http://www.cybermidi.com/privacy.php

Contact Us
Search:
Safeguarding Our Members' Privacy
Your privacy is very important to CYBERMIDI.com. Our Privacy Policy spells out CYBERMIDI's commitment to respecting the
privacy of CYBERMIDI.com members. CYBERMIDI.com reserves the right to change this policy, and we will notify you of any
changes.
Collection of Information on Our Members
Collection of information is usually grouped into two categories: personally identifiable information and so-called "aggregate" information. Personally identifiable information
is any information in CYBERMIDI's possession that is associated with a specific Member (such as a name or address) and information we collect about how individual Members use
CYBERMIDI.com (such as the fact that a Member visits music pages, or has purchased merchandise through CYBERMIDI.com.)
It does not include aggregate information, which is general demographic information (such as the total number of Members
who are more than 35 years old), or information which a Member has made public on CYBERMIDI.com.
Personally Identifiable Information
CYBERMIDI.com uses personal information only for the following purposes:
to process requests and orders placed with advertisers, merchants
and service providers on CYBERMIDI.com;
to personalize CYBERMIDI.com based on Members’ interests,
including making Members aware of editorial features, advertisements, and commercial offerings that may be of interest;
to communicate with Members, including promoting CYBERMIDI.com;
to register a Member for a contest or sweepstakes and to
administer or make related offers from the same;
to serve Members when they have questions or problems;
to perform normal business operations, such as billing, collection,
and accounting; and
to investigate complaints and protect CYBERMIDI.com and its
Members, in compliance with the law, the CYBERMIDI.com Member Agreement, Interactive Features Guidelines and CYBERMIDI.com policies.
CYBERMIDI.com respects the privacy of personal files in
Members’ computers. CYBERMIDI.com does not access, read,
upload or store data contained in or derived from private
files without the Member’s authorization. Once a Member
gives us that authorization, CYBERMIDI.com may from time
to time record information about your computer, communications
equipment, browser type and version number, mail application,
and operating system software (but no other non-CYBERMIDI.com
software). CYBERMIDI.com will use this information on an
individually-identifiable basis only to
analyze
how current or future CYBERMIDI.com features may operate
on your equipment;
available (such as memory or equipment upgrades).
of your connections.
CYBERMIDI.com uses strict procedures and safeguards designed
except with the specific consent of the sender or recipient,
or as specifically authorized or required by law.
Aggregate
Information
CYBERMIDI.com tracks the total number of visitors to each
of our pages within CYBERMIDI.com in an aggregate form to
allow us to update and improve our sites. Personally identifiable
information is not extracted in this process. CYBERMIDI.com
may use or disclose aggregated (not personally identifiable)
information for any purpose.
On a limited basis, we use "cookie" technology. Cookies
are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers
to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Our servers
then use these cookies to make your sessions easier by saving
your preferences while you are on CYBERMIDI.com pages. The
use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them
almost everywhere on the Internet. There are two cookies
used throughout CYBERMIDI.com pages. The first CYBERMIDI.com
cookie allows CYBERMIDI.com to know who the Member is and
that he or she properly authenticated into our network.
This cookie information can be used to retrieve personal
information needed during the Member session, for example,
to build your customized pages. The second cookie is an
"advertising" cookie which CYBERMIDI.com uses to keep track
of the ads the Member has seen. CYBERMIDI.com tracks which
ads have been viewed, and we tie it to Members’ demographic
data, but not to personally identifiable information. Remember,
this describes cookie usage ONLY on CYBERMIDI.com sites.
CYBERMIDI.com has no control over the use of cookies by
other Internet sites and their owners.
If a Member enters our pages from the site of one of CYBERMIDI's
partners, our system will recognize the path the visitor
has taken. Such partners are companies such as computer
or modem manufacturers with whom CYBERMIDI.com engages in
promotional deals. The benefits of these deals are often
passed on to CYBERMIDI.com Members.
Contact
Information
For answers to specific concerns regarding privacy that
are not addressed here, please write to us.
01/09/20  The Music Gallery: Can Music Ever Be Valued As Fine Art?
07/02/19  2019 International Songwriting Competition - Judges Announced
06/26/19  5 Quick Mixing Tips To Help Clean Up Your Music
08/12/18  How to Make a Digital Recording Studio
More posts...
More posts...
CYBERMIDI Classic Unlimited | ShopCYBERMIDI | Piano Wizard | MIDI Music Store | Sheet Music
his site is best viewed at 1024x768 or higher resolution, a Javascript enabled browser such as Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox.
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use | Become a member |
Licensing | Advertising
Printable Catalog | Backing Tracks for Perfomers | Affiliate Program |
Price list | Security |
FAQs | Contact Us
©2019 CYBERMIDI.com inc. All Rights Reserved.
